Research is meant to benefit society by raising public awareness and creating products and innovations that enhance development.
研究的本意是通过提高公众意识、创造能促进发展的产品和创新成果来造福社会。
For research to serve its full purpose, the results must leave the confines of research laboratories and academic journals.
要让研究充分发挥作用，研究成果就必须走出研究实验室和学术期刊的局限。
Findings effectively communicated can go a long way to serve the interests of the public.
研究成果若能得到有效传播，就能在很大程度上造福公众。
They can help address social injustices or improve treatments offered to patients.
这些成果能帮助解决社会不公问题，或改进为患者提供的治疗。
Many researchers seem to be content with sharing the results of their studies in academic journals or at conferences.
许多研究人员似乎满足于在学术期刊或会议上分享自己的研究成果。
But few journals allow everybody to read the findings.
但允许所有人阅读这些研究成果的期刊寥寥无几。
Even articles freely available are usually written in academic language incomprehensible to the average reader.
即使是可以免费获取的文章，通常也是用普通读者无法理解的学术语言写成的。
For researchers in the tenure-track system, their main goal is winning tenure, which in part can be achieved by getting a number of papers published in prominent journals.
对处在终身教职考核体系中的研究人员而言，主要目标是获得终身教职，而这在一定程度上可以通过在知名期刊上发表若干篇论文来实现。
Pressures like this mean community-level outreach is not prioritised.
诸如此类的压力意味着，社区层面的推广工作得不到优先考虑。
Many researchers lack the writing skills to describe their results to a general audience.
许多研究人员缺乏向普通受众描述自己研究成果的写作能力。
They may also worry about whether the public will understand their findings, or about findings being used to influence controversial policies.
他们可能还担心公众能否理解自己的研究成果，或者担心研究成果被用来影响有争议的政策。
These concerns cause some researchers to shy away from communicating their findings outside the academic community.
这些顾虑使一些研究人员回避在学术界以外传播自己的研究成果。
Propagating research findings beyond academic publications is particularly crucial for addressing certain social disparities.
将研究成果传播到学术出版物以外，对于解决某些社会差距问题尤为关键。
It can help families, communities, healthcare providers, policymakers, government agencies and other stakeholders to understand and respond to crises that plague society.
这样做能帮助家庭、社区、医疗服务提供者、政策制定者、政府机构和其他利益相关者认识并应对困扰社会的危机。
The benefits of sharing findings flow both ways.
分享研究成果带来的好处是双向的。
Engaging with other researchers and the public can lead to unexpected new connections and new ideas that could suggest fruitful new directions for research.
与其他研究人员和公众交流互动，能够带来意想不到的新联系和新想法，而这些联系和想法或许能为研究指出富有成效的新方向。
For the benefit of both researchers and the communities, the need to find innovative, accessible ways to share the work cannot be overstated.
为了研究人员和社区双方的利益，寻找创新而通俗易懂的方式来分享研究成果，其必要性怎么强调都不为过。
Institutions and funding organisations should support more researchers to publish in open access journals so that the public doesn’t have to pay to read them.
各机构和资助组织应该支持更多研究人员在开放获取期刊上发表论文，这样公众就不必付费阅读这些期刊了。
Institutions and researchers should invest in partnerships that expand capacity for sharing results more broadly.
各机构和研究人员应该投入资源发展合作伙伴关系，以增强更广泛地分享研究成果的能力。
Furthermore, ethics committees should make it mandatory for researchers to share their results with the public.
此外，伦理委员会应该规定，研究人员必须与公众分享自己的研究成果。
Every research participant should opt in or out of receiving results, as part of the process of giving informed consent.
作为知情同意程序的一部分，每位研究参与者都应选择是否接收研究结果。
There could be misunderstanding of the findings presented by the researcher because of technical terms.
由于涉及专业术语，人们对研究人员所展示的研究成果可能会产生误解。
But this can be resolved by researchers engaging the services of professional writers or communication officers to help with translating their study into more accessible language and share it widely with media outlets and the public.
但研究人员可以聘请专业写作人员或传播专员来解决这个问题，请他们帮忙把自己的研究转化为更通俗易懂的语言，并与媒体机构和公众广泛分享。
Sharing results with the people who are most affected by them makes us better researchers and ensures that our work can be used to improve people’s lives.
与受研究成果影响最大的人分享成果，能让我们成为更好的研究人员，并确保我们的研究能用来改善人们的生活。
Institutions and collaborators must recognise the value of doing so.
各机构和合作者必须认识到这样做的价值。